<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Owen Churches&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Owen Churches&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Churchill Fellowship Part 1 - Where do they go?</title>
      <link>/post/2019/06/14/what-is-a-churchill-fellowship-part-1-where-do-they-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/06/14/what-is-a-churchill-fellowship-part-1-where-do-they-go/</guid>
      <description>The Churchill Fellowship presents an amazing opportunity for Australians to:
 Travel overseas for 4-8 weeks to investigate inspiring practices around a topic or issue you are passionate about! Use the new knowledge and experience you gain from experts and specialists from around the world to make a difference in Australia.
 I began thinking in earnest about applying for a fellowship in January 2018. But it was a bit overwhelming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistical history hour</title>
      <link>/post/2019/06/06/statistical-history-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/06/06/statistical-history-hour/</guid>
      <description>A delightful side product of my Churchill fellowship in 2019 was the opportunity to visit a bunch of places in the United Kingdom that are important for various moments in statistical history. During the trip I tweeted some gratuitous selfies at some of these locations. So, this is a blog post to:
Bring together the pictures and stories of those locations Extend the idea of visiting statistically significant locations as a tour using the TSP package to solve the problem of visiting these locations in the most efficient order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legislative Network in South Australia</title>
      <link>/post/2019/06/03/legislative-network-in-south-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/06/03/legislative-network-in-south-australia/</guid>
      <description>Background I joined the public service in 2017. Pretty soon after I started my boss and new colleagues suggested that the most important thing for me to read would be the legislation that I work under1.
The thing is, when reading my legislation, I realised that it referenced several other pieces of legislation. This meant that to fully understand my legislation I also had to read these referenced pieces of legislation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Its my pleasure</title>
      <link>/post/2019/05/16/its-my-pleasure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/05/16/its-my-pleasure/</guid>
      <description>Background When we look for a film to watch on Netflix, the interface we see presents us not with an open list of all the movies stored on the service but rather with a curated, personal set of recommendations for films. Similar processes guide us to find food to eat, friends to meet and lead us toward our choices whenever we interact withe the world through an online platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR  Public sector statistician Former neuroscienctist   Long version The past I completed my PhD at the Univeristy of Cambridge in 2011 and until 2017, I was a neuroscientist. There is a good list of my academic publications here. I quite enjoyed a lot about being an academic. I did some lectures where I lead the class in protest against the tyranny of frequentist statistics1:
  And I was sometimes joined for lectures by a virtual teaching assistant.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>